So much has happened.
Every day was new and different.
The Journey Begins
I won't pretend I remember all of it.
Katagiri High School 63rd Graduation Ceremony
Most of the memories have
faded and vanished,
Katagiri High School 63rd Graduation Ceremony
but many are just as vivid
as the day they happened.
Katagiri High School 63rd Graduation Ceremony
I'm sure they're...
Kyoto!
Fall leaves!
Temples!
Yeah.
Yuki sure is excited.
Look at all the trees—
Yoshikawa, cool your jets.
Toru, don't boss me around!
Ow!
Like a parent and child...
It's Yuki's first time in Kyoto,
so she's raring to go.
I got to come here in middle school.
It's always Kyoto, isn't it?
My school trip was here, too.
But now that we're high schoolers, we get to
explore more on our own, which is great.
Yeah.
Except at night...
That's right, Miyamura...
How are you going to bathe?
I don't think I can.
I'm prepared to go without
for the whole trip.
The girls have baths in their rooms,
but the guys have to use the public one.
Also, what about changing clothes?
I'll change in the bathroom.
I see.
Good luck.
Am I even going to enjoy this trip?
Is he even going to enjoy this trip?
There you are!
Took you guys long enough!
Hey, Shu.
Yo!
No one else is here, though.
Not a soul.
I bet your yelling scared them off.
What was that?!
Check this out!
Souvenirs from the shop up ahead!
They looked too good to pass up!
He bought souvenirs on the first day?!
Shu, what are you doing loading up when
we haven't even been to the hotel yet?
That's a good point!
Wanna eat 'em, then?
Want some, Miyamura?
Huh? Um, I...
I can't believe he bought
souvenirs on the first day.
Where'd all her excitement go?
Oh, are you and Iura-kun in the same room?
Laugh      Laugh
Yeah, but Ishikawa-kun's with us, too.
Flash
I hope things work out...
I have a feeling they won't.
Class Trip
The bed's so soft!
This room is even better than I expected!
They said we're free until dinner,
but there's nothing to do.
Yeah.
Want to hit up another room?
Oh, like the boys' rooms?
There you go again!
Who picked up the key?
Shu. Shu has it.
Where the hell is he?
What are you guys doing?
Hey, Mizouchi, do you know where Shu is?
He's got our room key.
Iura?
I saw him walk into the room a minute ago.
Shu, you jerk! Open the door!
Ishikawa-kun, calm down!
C'mon, like I said... I'm sorry...
At least let us in the room
before you take a nap, dumbass!
Anyway, now that our stuff's in the room,
we can relax until dinnertime.
Yeah, guess you're right.
How long do we have?
Hang on. I'll check—
Day 1
18:00-
Public bath (Boys only)
18:00- Class 1, Groups 1-4
18:30- Class 1, Group 5 & Class 2, Groups 1-2
30-minute bath time
Class 2, Groups 3 and up will bathe at 20:00 after dinner.
Shu, wake up!
Sure...
Class 1, Group 1
Maybe I'll take a nap, too.
Wait, don't we need to bathe before dinner?
Public bath (Boys only)
18:00- Class 1, Groups 1-4
Do we?
Oh crap.
Miyamura, bath time!
Men
Bath
N-No!
What are you talking about? Let's go already!
I... I, uh...
I'll bathe later.
Hey, hurry it up, group 1!
We're all waiting!
H-Help me, Ishikawa-kun...
Miyamura, you're not feeling well, right?
You're not feeling well? Do you have a fever?
Is it a cold?
N-No, i-it's not a cold...
Going for broke
Shu, Miyamura's on his period.
Huh?
I-I-Is that right...?
Going for broke
Yeah.
Hey, what's taking so long?
Get in the bath already!
Shut up!
We're having an existential crisis here!
Huh?!
Miyamura, I did good, right?
Yeah, good job.
And goodbye.
Huh?
Hey, Miyamura.
Hori-san...
I'm apparently on my period.
Says the guy who got
a perfect score in phys ed?!
Wait, is that your excuse to get
out of a bath? That's hilarious!
So how are you gonna bathe today?
My period's giving me cramps,
so I'll go without.
Want to use the shower in our room?
Yuki went to visit a friend
and won't be back for a while.
Won't we get in trouble for a guy
going into a girl's room?
Er, you don't have to if you don't want to.
I'm alive again...
C'mon, you coulda used the hair dryer.
Well, I'm sure I could have,
but I didn't want to take too long.
Any word from Yoshikawa-san?
Not yet.
Okay.
I should get my stuff ready for tomorrow.
Hori-san...
Would you let just any guy into your
room if they were in a tight spot?
You really shouldn't.
Of course I wouldn't.
Really?
Really.
But you let me in.
Well, you're...
Not like that, right?
You're... fine, okay?
Since you're...
I'm what?
Y-You wouldn't t-try anything, right?
Are you sure?
Well, I'll head on back to my room.
Thanks for letting me use your shower.
Hey, wait—
Even if I said he could try something,
he wouldn't, right?
What was that about letting
other guys into my room?
I took her towel with me...
Oh, Miyamura.
Hey, Miyamura, gonna put on a yukata?
Did you go somewhere?
Oh, yeah. Sorta.
Whoa, look! There are maiko here!
Don't point!
Whoa! Hey there, ladies!
Don't wave at them!
You two have no idea
how to behave in public!
I'll return your towel later.
It's fine. We have plenty.
More importantly, what about tonight?
The bath.
If you're coming over, I'll handle Yuki.
Oh, don't worry.
I can always take the late bath
for people who miss theirs.
Anyone who misses their designated bath time can bathe after 23:00.
Oh, I see...
I should have read it more carefully.
Sorry.
Don't be.
Thanks for waiting.
It's all yours.
Are you sure?
Now I feel stupid for thinking
so much about how to respond.
And why the hell didn't you read the rules?!
Hori?
Are you gonna use the bath?
I am! And I'm gonna be in there until 11:00!
You'll be totally wrinkled.
This class trip really flew by.
It sure did.
It won't be easy, but it's time
to say goodbye to Kyoto.
At least we took lots of pics.
Oh, I've still got space for more!
Hori, gimme a peace sign!
Hey, cut it out!
I'll print some pictures
and give you a copy.
Thanks.
Counting the ones our teacher
took, we'll have a ton.
Here's one of Iura messing with Toru.
That was really funny.
Here's you stuffing your face.
I hope we can all come
back together sometime.
Yeah.
Hee Hee
Hey! It's time to meet up at the buses!
Got it!
Man, I can't believe
we're going home already.
I'll race you to the bus!
You're on!
Miyamura.
This was a pretty good class trip.
Yeah, it was.
Hurry up, you two!
Yeah, coming!
Miyamura-kun...?
Wow, it is you! You cut your hair!
W-Wait! Turn off the hose first!
Oh, right!
Sorry about that.
You really got soaked.
It's okay. I'll wring out my clothes later.
That won't do!
You need to dry off with a towel.
Let's go to the clinic.
The clinic?
Clinic
Here.
Ah, thanks.
No one's here. Are we allowed
to just use the towels?
Why not take off your cardigan?
I'll just leave it on.
I've been wondering...
Why do you always stay all covered up?
You didn't even bathe with
the other guys during the class trip.
All of the boys pick swimming for phys ed,
but you always pick running.
Th-The council president runs
during swimming time, too!
Oh, I don't mind Sengoku-kun doing it.
Why not?!
Actually, Sengoku-kun told me
you always change clothes
in the bathroom or an empty classroom.
Wants to know
So, why is that?
Crap. She's more persistent than I thought.
What?!
I thought you might actually
be a girl or something.
Do I look like a girl to you?
Ah, so she's suspicious.
I feel like she's gonna find me out.
I'm exhausted.
And hot.
So you do get hot in that.
Y'know, I had a thought.
Something like a vest
Why not wear something like this?
My arms would show.
Ah...
Yet you'll wear a sailor-style uniform.
This is my old middle school uniform.
Try it on when you have the chance!
I don't want to try it on
even when I have the chance.
I don't know why Hori-san wants me to.
I'll just put it on and
tell her it was too small.
There's no way it'll fit.
Oh, Toru-kun.
Come on in.
It fits...
Sorry to barge in like this.
He's in his room.
I'm coming in!
Oh, sorry, Miyamura.
Could you let me look at your textbook?
I forgot mine at school.
Is something wrong?
Hey!
Not now!
Please not now!
I-It's not what you think, Ishikawa-kun!
This is...
Yeah, it looks good.
It wasn't what it looked like!
What, so you won't wear one again?
You should try it.
Ah, but your hair could be...
A little longer. Just a bit.
Shoulder length.
Or just enough to hide your ears.
Can you stop playing mental dress-up with me?
I've got it.
Just grow it out for six months.
Now you're deciding things?!
Why? What's so great about
sailor-style uniforms?!
You used to hate them!
No, I didn't! I told you last time, but—
Like I remember!
I seem to run into them a lot.
President!
Sengoku!
Shudder
Sailor uniforms or blazers?!
Which is better?!
Huh?!
The sailor style looks great on girls, right?
That silhouette leaves me speechless.
No, it's gotta be a blazer.
They work with neckties or ribbons.
Right, President?
What are you two talking about?
You know! How it gets a man going
when he sees girls in clothes he likes!
Oh, so your preferences?
Yes! Ishikawa-kun says the sailor style
is better and won't listen.
I actually prefer tracksuits.
Whoa, is he serious?
What?! Athletic wear is good, right?!
Sengoku, just be honest.
You like the school swimsuits, don't you?
Really, President? That's a bit much!
That's not what I said!
Either that or gym bloomers.
What year do you think it is?!
Then what's in nowadays?
Now it's those... navy socks, right?
Miyamura likes blazers.
Oh, and black knee-highs are good, too.
Acquiring odd intel
Yeah, I get you!
Oh, I don't mind Sengoku-kun doing it.
Why not?!
Sengoku-kun, your shirt
looks a little baggy.
Does it? I think it's the same as always.
I like his slender body.
He's self-conscious about being too thin
and puts shirts on under his white one.
I know all about it.
No way!
Student Counseling
What's wrong?
Didn't you know?
Swimming is optional, but all the boys
have to do it on the last day.
N-No one told us!
They changed the rule this year.
You got a notice about it.
And you can't be absent without good reason.
Like a broken leg?
Don't be rash, Miyamura-kun!
This isn't fair!
Why only the boys?
Right?! I couldn't agree more!
We're on different pages!
I'm perpetually amazed that
they let you be a teacher.
I'm pretty smart, you know.
And I like high school girls.
They should come and arrest you.
Hey now.
Why not just do it?
It's one day in the pool.
Can I keep my clothes on?
I'd like to as well.
Are you trying to drown?
So you don't want to take your clothes off?
My clothes are like skin to me.
A second skin.
Would you have me rip off my own skin
and then sit out in the scorching sun?
Calm down, Sengoku.
Extra! "Cruel School Skins Student!"
Don't go making up headlines.
Four days until pool day...
If only the world would end.
Oh, Sensei, I have an excuse for that day.
What, you're gonna skip?
Four days from now will overlap
with my 28-day cycle.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
That's no fair, Miyamura-kun!
Sensei, I have the same excuse for that day!
President!
Just cut the crap!
Shutting up
No matter how much you whine,
you're not getting out of this.
Oh, I see.
That's too bad, I guess.
Wh-What's going on, Miyamura-kun?
Sensei, I don't own a swimsuit.
Well, not to worry.
The school is prepared,
so they'll let you rent one.
That's great news, Miyamura-kun.
Yeah...
I just don't understand
why there's no pool day for the girls.
Because there are guys like you
at the school. Get a clue.
I never should've applied to Katagiri High.
But then you never would've met Hori.
Don't sell me short.
I'd have found a way to meet her.
Don't mess with me.
Now you wanna get expelled?
I hope that when I wake up in four days,
my right arm will have exploded.
Can't you just fake a cold?
Okay, a cold it is.
A cold that will blow up my arm.
What kind of colds do you catch?
You've got it good though, President.
You can at least wear a swimsuit.
What burden do you bear, Miyamura?
What? You embarrassed about
putting on a swimsuit, Miyamura?
How's getting in the pool
in a swimsuit any better than coming
Serious
to English class in your birthday suit?
You're talking to your English teacher, dolt.
I'd rather be publicly guillotined
than be seen in a swimsuit.
Why is this a matter
of life or death for you, Sengoku?
Well, I can tell that you guys
really don't want to get in the pool.
I'll talk to Sasaki-sensei.
What?!
F-F-For real?!
Speak to your elders politely.
Thanks a bunch!
Yeah, that still coulda been better.
Will you really talk to Sasaki-sensei?
I will, but no promises.
It's a teacher's duty to listen
to students' concerns and find solutions!
Intense
Don't put it like that.
You're making me nervous.
Four days from now,
we will not be undressing!
And you're getting bolder.
You'll both still need a reason.
Miyamura-kun is on his period,
and I'll be in an explosion.
That's all.
Is that really what you want me to say?
No, not really.
We arrived at those through
extensive compromising.
This is gonna be a pain.
What a big relief, though.
I wasn't sure what I'd do.
I wanna hit the beach.
Huh?!
Woo-hoo!
Shu, no cannonballs!
The pool is the best!
Aren't you hot, Miyamura-kun?
No, I am, but I'll be fine.
You're making me hot, too!
Get that deck clean, you slackers!
Yes, sir.
Man, my feet are hot.
Don't you have sandals, President?
Remi took them before I got here.
Sengoku, why not come in for a dip?
I would if no one else was around.
You're like one of the girls!
Sengoku-san!
You're asking for it!
Bring it on! Bring it, bring it!
Ow...
We were just clowning around a little..
Quit clowning around and get to work!
You okay?
Are you two shrinking violets doing your job?
Oh, Kyo-chan!
What's with the surprise?
You on your way home?
The girls only had to come for the morning.
See ya!
Hey, Remi, my sandals!
Not a chance!
I'm not giving them back!
Are those sandals cool?
Yep, nice and cool.
I heard girls!
What?!
Ayasaki's feet are exposed!
You're right! They're so cute!
Get back in the water, you pervy kappas!
Sengoku's pissed!
The president is scary!
What are they doing?
I told you to clean!
Yes, sir.
Why clean it when it's not even dirty?
My thoughts exactly.
Hey.
How's it going?
Our messiah.
Messiah
Don't call me that. You're being pains.
Miyamura, aren't you hot in that?
Yes, of course I am.
Why do you look tired of hearing that?
Why did you come, Sensei?
The girls left, so I got bored.
Now there're only guys around.
Yeah, that's what I figured.
Yasuda-sensei!
It's Terajima-sensei...
I put you in charge of the boys'
tutoring session, didn't I?!
Are you stupid or something?!
Yeah, I might be.
He just said he was smart four days ago.
Honestly, I don't have time for this!
See ya.
Man, Sengoku, your legs are so thin!
It's not like it's on purpose.
What's your hips measurement?
I don't know.
So, what's the deal, Sengoku? Can't swim?
Don't mess with me.
I'm invincible in the water.
I'm perfectly at home in the water.
It is my domain.
Then what're you doing on land?
I really like swimming, too.
That's rich coming from a guy
who's skipping pool day.
Well, I know Miyamura wants
to keep his tattoos a secret...
Ow! A cramp! My foot cramped!
Shu, you idiot!
You did that Inugami Clan
handstand thing, didn't you?
No... but I won't deny it.
Which is it?
Come to think of it, why are Sengoku-san
and Miyamura excused today?
They seem fine.
Sengoku's arm blew up,
and Miyamura's on his period.
Oh...
Huh?!
Well, it's summer, so there're
bound to be a few explosions.
Next time
page.2 Cooking Class